I have the welcome to Megamind Today We can start event Stop me safe path Nasa
我今天欢迎来到Megamind我们可以开始活动让我停下安全之路美国航空航天局
Chris Lake in English and would study which I know what makes it appears at
克里斯·雷克（Chris Lake）用英语学习，我知道这是什么使它出现在
Mega save All American Spirit Mage steak with new like were off and reverse Apink
超级节省所有带有新赞似的美式精神法师牛排，并关闭Apink
perfect English is to do it ok to make you safe What is a good student Winner
完美的英语可以确保您的安全。什么是一个好的学生获胜者
stade de Los and the next time you've changed When she stands at our attention
洛斯体育场（Stade de Los）和您下次的变化当她引起我们的注意时
to the world University is paid attention to stay Together talk about
去世界大学留学留心在一起聊一聊
and next time you speak english Numbers of memories with something about Play
下次您说英语时，您会发现一些关于Play的回忆
music weather and fantastical bridge westlife westlife stateless make their
音乐天气和梦幻般的桥westlife westlife无国籍使他们
music number one is Super almond something that you're All I didn't even
音乐第一是超级杏仁，这就是我所没有的
take off one's stomach are you Happy Birthday you can send some
放下肚子，你生日快乐，你可以送一些
body Butter which failed three seconds and adjacent to the person That is the
身体黄油，失败了三秒钟，并与人相邻
walking transformation in English is used to make Somebody achievements for
英语中的步行转换用于取得某人的成就。
example some Little amelie intermingled promotion is complete guide you Heart Is
例如，一些小混血的提升完全可以指导您
suggested patients with something Brand New Heaven Is invalid Write what I feel
建议患者使用全新的天堂是无效的写我的感觉
Pretty with some impeccable examples and instruction helping hand printing and
带有一些无可挑剔的示例和说明的漂亮手稿有助于手工印刷和
testament toeic247 Quynh I have something that having seen everything
遗嘱toeic247 Quynh我已经看到了一切
you hear me live stream composition to show The Voice levels you telling
您会听到我实时流组成，以显示您所讲的语音水平
moneyless is to the treatment is against the converted Australia all your
一分钱一分货都是对付转化后的澳大利亚的一切
accessibility Osho event Attention Thien Will I want to just like you
辅助功能Osho事件注意Thien我想跟你一样
Save The White as efficiently Pretty love you faid calculation And you can
有效地将白色保存为漂亮的爱，可以轻松计算
save us and reduce pollution in Bill does not call research suggests that
拯救我们并减少污染，比尔不呼吁研究表明
and you'll be the one to your hair fashion Trend for me and you say Happy
对我来说，你将是你的发型时尚趋势之一，你说快乐
birthday for scientists and Happy Birthday initialization something just
科学家生日快乐和生日快乐初始化只是
happened and another person with its importance on my Instagram wardriving
发生了，另一个人对我的Instagram追赶很重要
folders for me Because they speak english with every single Day And I call
给我的文件夹，因为他们每一天都说英语，所以我打电话
the world time you got some countries in a way that it comin from and becoming a
世界时间，您以某种方式来自某些国家，并成为一种
transcript Of Your language in the English in your heart and the west mum's
您心中英文和西方妈妈的英语成绩单
is insufficient Michigan basis is Some people Pretty and ca
是密歇根州的基础不足是一些人漂亮和ca
two iPhones created work Yesterday When I speak English Russian English and tried
两部iPhone创造了作品昨天当我说英语俄语英语并尝试
To think of words and lots of values ​​Tokyo which occurs in many cases
想想很多情况下发生的单词和很多价值的东京
completely different video is for you wanna make most EVN Days from Yours you
完全不同的视频适合您，您想从中获得最多的EVN天
vietnamese were entirely different with New Year Come Together to stay connected
越南与“新年齐聚”保持联系完全不同
and the tree didn't need to your retirement age re-perfect reserve and
那棵树不需要您的退休年龄重新完善储备，并且
people on the racquet pudding grace in the store to feel you really want things
商店里球拍布丁上的人们觉得你真的想要东西
and your one person on kerapoxy non-touristy area and I Knew he would
和你的一个人在喀拉帕克非旅游区，我知道他会
think going on Vietnamese wives of your English learning for adjusting atlanta
认为去学习英语的越南妻子去调整亚特兰大
many Families and every fascapin herramientas ultracurve will help you
许多家庭和每一个fascapin herramientas超曲线都将为您提供帮助
improve your friends live and work together we love yourself and Made
改善您的朋友的生活和合作，我们爱自己，并取得了
above convertible all the essential base with Real Madrid deflated America
高于敞篷车，所有必不可少的基础，皇马都lated缩了美国
with So Beautiful Girls and decay is time to very very much happier asakura
与《如此美丽的女孩》和《衰落》是时候让非常快乐的朝仓
holi holi Vitamin A just want our people going to reduce your workday freak out
维生素A只是希望我们的员工减少您的工作日困扰
of herself In Me Myself and You can take the mansion report for Visual friend
自己在“我自己”中，您可以为视觉朋友获得豪宅报告
for people to take an selected full name UT massa marinated unaware of and my
让人们不加选择地将选定的全名UT Massa腌制了下来，而我
brother and then you save you i don't wanna go I want to put my show tonight
兄弟，然后你救了你，我不想走，我想今晚放我的表演
with me the English Translator Glee the music the perfect finished unified and cross
和我一起，英语翻译Glee完美地完成了音乐的制作和交融
of any job interview Shell garakuta live show evangelical short while I was
我在任职期间接受壳牌加拉古塔现场直播的任何福音采访中
suggested this game is safe II Don't Want any reason I'm going to
建议这款游戏安全II不想要任何理由
be looking for Myself I worked for Myself the music your way you want to
寻找自己我为自己工作音乐以您想要的方式
take offence are you Because internet free shop well well you said our vehicle
冒犯你是因为互联网免费商店很好，你说我们的车
kinh welbike my soul us against abuse and to my shop nice occurred while the
肯·维尔贝克（Kinh Welbike）我的灵魂是我们免受虐待，而到了我的商店，
world Pink Rup Cookin yourself What does she know the marriage of standing with
世界Pink Rup Cookin自己她知道与站在一起的婚姻
Greek words of buddhist nun Stay The wild about so you can understand and shopping
佛教尼姑的希腊单词“ Stay The Wild”，以便您可以理解和购物
bands and wait for it Myself and make up very speak When you are packing
乐队等着我自己，而且很会说话当你打包时
something of used to drink some thing gonna make you Sick Asus something in my
曾经喝点东西的东西会让你生病的华硕在我身上的东西
video and Live Once they speak of the age when you doing something you She
视频和直播一旦他们说出自己做某事的年龄，她
paid to meet you have prepared to use and parties
支付满足您准备使用的费用并参加聚会
a worse they take you Seek Pika speak of Minsk Washington show if you speaking
更糟糕的是，如果您说话，他们会让您寻求皮卡（Seek Pika）谈论明斯克华盛顿（Minsk Washington）表演
something of you speak english from the world will you complete Storm school
你们中的一些人会说来自世界各地的英语，您会完成暴风学校
with cicumin for iPad Bach Tuyet met with Vinamilk Missing something speaking aloud
与西葫芦一起在iPad上使用巴赫·图耶特（Bach Tuyet）与Vinamilk见面
News lactamases understand the different Hye Krystal well-paid reshade.me since
自从新闻内酰胺了解了Hye Krystal高薪的reshade.me之后，
and competitiveness I have tim here for to with Ava I have spent her Friends my
和竞争力，我在这里与Ava在一起，我花了她的Friends my
monster clothes of with continuous tense with some Time To Want Some period
持续紧张的怪物衣服，需要一些时间
of time and she whispered We save and we need to have that moment of time and
时间，她小声说：“我们保存了，我们需要那一刻的时间，
depart for nhung's Birthday one nine semantic World Tower of property and and
离开nhung的生日，一幢九层语义世界财产塔，以及
adapt and talk show when you are you can use the work the period of
适应和脱口秀时，您可以在工作期间使用
time you since You can see you since when it's that time part time and that
时间，因为你可以看到你，因为那是时候兼职，那
connects the words in Spanish of Gold Dragon Ball When I would something the
连接“ Gold Dragon Ball”（西班牙语）中的“ Gold Dragon Ball”（金龙珠）西班牙语中的单词
music you take something kompany couldn't answer Me That I need your iPad
音乐，你带了某某东西，我无法回答我我需要你的iPad
Words Together When the lights turned down and give it to you announced and announced
在一起的话当灯光熄灭并通知你时，宣布
that American Boys have Only a refined When you are Taking me Mary mackillop
当你带我去玛丽·麦克基洛普时，美国男孩只有一个精致的人
iPad I say yes i can hold you my iPad normally used to say I can give my iPad
iPad我说是的，我可以抱着你，我的iPad通常用来说我可以给我的iPad
turn on morning Will Keep something to somebody Valentine siddharth mallya when
打开早晨将保留某物给某人Valentine siddharth mallya当
mai much money and you need to keep our countries is excited You are very nice
赚了很多钱，你需要让我们的国家兴奋不已
to suspect that occur in to me à Thàng Khánh University of life My
怀疑发生在我生命中的ThàngKhánh大学
career and currently we swim in it right to have withered and Music is a occurring
事业，目前我们正朝着枯萎的方向游泳，音乐正在发生
per week and speakers Who use the flesh is having a baby once it have our way
每周，演讲者谁使用肉体，一旦我们成功，就会生一个孩子
you to save The Dragon Pearl Cruise incorrect when you save file can I help
您保存文​​件时保存的“龙珠游轮”不正确，我可以帮忙吗
protect your current health Which you have mind Right now visa Brazil sample
保护您目前的健康现在就签证巴西样品
rate was something that Life is something that I have tried
速度是我尝试过的生活
he means I can't live stream interval practical for you can syntastic and
他的意思是我不能直播时间间隔，因为您可以合成和
intent A circuit arts colleges and don't
意向电路艺术学院，不要
understand you shop We here I'm standing out other partners And you my friend
了解您的商店我们在这里与其他合作伙伴脱颖而出，而您是我的朋友
Hills and me to ISO on her feet with the Sake of things I said something Nice to
我和希尔斯（Hills）一起走上了ISO之路，我对我说的话很高兴
meet you want to agree with another friend you say me neither Mini World
见面，你想同意另一个朋友，你说我都不是迷你世界
Miss Poet about a girl. Where is Hung?
我的姐姐诗人关于一个女孩，洪迷在哪里？妖精的尾巴迷你游戏越南灵魂
skirt with Green button on the other hand affairs of Sugar đ my father Take
糖affairs父亲的另一件事是带有绿色纽扣的裙子。
me to iwantim Fresh from someone I want just wanna Thank you save me this is
我到iwantim我想要的人新鲜谢谢你救救我这是
open When were thrown IV IC in either double or press And witness The Wings of
打开两次或按两次IV集成电路投掷时见证的翅膀。
Fate which They work well how people play with friends and threats and tried
他们与人如何与朋友和威胁玩耍并尝试过的命运很好
many time on my Instagram Anyone Spirit of Bright starts comment rate and then i
很多时候，我的Instagram上的Anything Spirit of Bright开始发表评论，然后我
just take What's weather today and the and for that can sell my soul is English
就拿今天的天气来说，能卖出我的灵魂的就是英语
with you when I come and take you take you tell me cause i made a
和你在一起，当我来带你带你告诉我，因为我做了一个
at the temple to Toeic is how I faint wish exact we have worked out War Of Life
在托比奇神庙（Toeic）是我微弱地希望我们完成了《生命之战》（War of Life）
people work and utilize and not certain objects the world of What We
人们工作和利用，而不是某些物体，我们的世界
want to compare on the left off bufet However such As I know what you see how
想要比较左边的bufet但是，例如，我知道你怎么看
much progress with the heaven in comparison with your own descriptions
与您自己的描述相比，天堂有了很大的进步
show us How And Snow White sat how what is right down forests and so my
向我们展示How and Snow White坐在森林附近是怎么回事，所以我的
Collection the value of the valley and you know you've tried to make you work I
收集山谷的价值，你就知道自己在努力使自己工作
learn English in you Nothing is on the world of record that person and with you
用你的语言学英语没有任何东西可以记录那个人和你
on the switches to hear the best fastest way to you the way the Contest and
在交换机上以最快的方式聆听与您进行比赛和比赛的方式
refresh to see you in my experience Bye bye anh
刷新以我的经验与您见面再见再见